<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Certified Devices on Matterize Labs - Your Matter Smart Home Development Partner</title><link>https://matterize.io/certified-devices/</link><description>Recent content in Certified Devices on Matterize Labs - Your Matter Smart Home Development Partner</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:35:45 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matterize.io/certified-devices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Espressif Systems — Certified Devices</title><link>https://matterize.io/certified-devices/espressifs-ystems/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:35:45 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://matterize.io/certified-devices/espressifs-ystems/</guid><description>Espressif Systems is a global leader in wireless communication technologies, consistently pushing the boundaries of IoT innovation. Its portfolio of certified devices showcases a commitment to quality, security, and interoperability across a broad range of IoT solutions.</description></item><item><title>Nordic Semiconductor — Certified Devices and Ecosystem</title><link>https://matterize.io/certified-devices/nordic-semiconductor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:35:45 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://matterize.io/certified-devices/nordic-semiconductor/</guid><description>Nordic Semiconductor is a world-leading provider of ultra-low-power wireless solutions, enabling cutting-edge connectivity across a range of IoT applications. The company’s certified devices and modules power some of the most advanced smart products on the market today.</description></item><item><title>NXP Semiconductors — Certified Devices and Solutions</title><link>https://matterize.io/certified-devices/nxp-semiconductors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:35:45 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://matterize.io/certified-devices/nxp-semiconductors/</guid><description>NXP Semiconductors is a global leader in secure connectivity solutions for the automotive, industrial, and consumer markets. With a focus on sustainability, security, and intelligent systems, NXP enables breakthrough products that power the modern world.</description></item><item><title>Renesas Electronics Corporation — Certified Devices and Solutions</title><link>https://matterize.io/certified-devices/renesas-electronics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:35:45 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://matterize.io/certified-devices/renesas-electronics/</guid><description>Renesas Electronics Corporation is a global leader in semiconductor solutions, empowering industries with cutting-edge microcontrollers (MCUs), system-on-chips (SoCs), analog, and power devices. Renesas’s comprehensive product portfolio supports a wide range of industries, from automotive and industrial to healthcare and consumer electronics.</description></item><item><title>Silicon Labs — Certified Devices and IoT Development Platform</title><link>https://matterize.io/certified-devices/silicon-labs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:35:45 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://matterize.io/certified-devices/silicon-labs/</guid><description>Silicon Labs is a global leader in secure, intelligent wireless technology, enabling developers to bring innovative IoT solutions to market faster and more reliably. With a focus on integrated hardware, software, and ecosystem support, Silicon Labs empowers developers across smart home, industrial, healthcare, and more.</description></item><item><title>Dendo SCM Smart Shade</title><link>https://matterize.io/certified-devices/dendo-scm-smart-shade/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:59:48 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://matterize.io/certified-devices/dendo-scm-smart-shade/</guid><description>Built in collaboration with Dendo. Matter-certified by the Connectivity Standards Alliance. Designed for seamless smart shade automation across platforms.</description></item></channel></rss>